You're not working! How would you
like a job in home health care?
(Penny:)Not a chance.
(Bernadette:)-Please. I'm desperate.
-No.
(Bernadette:)-I'll pay you anything you want.
-Okay, then, yeah.
No! Keep your money!
(Bernadette:)I could've ridden
a bull longer than that.
(Leonard:)What you working on?
(Sheldon:)I'm writing an appeal
to the Faculty Senate,
(Sheldon:)so that I can move
on from string theory.
(Leonard:)How's it going?
(Sheldon:)You tell me.
"Dear esteemed colleagues,
(Sheldon:)As you may know, I have requested
to change my field of study.
(Sheldon:)My decision to do so is, I believe,
in the best interest of science.
(Sheldon:)At your convenience,
I'd be happy to explain it to you
in words you'll understand?
(Leonard:)It's nice that
you called them esteemed.
(Sheldon:)You're right. I'll take that out.